scissors glue burns card the details
剪刀胶烧卡的详细信息
关于这些的所有解释都在v-folds中
scissors glue burns card the details
about these are all explained in v-folds
教程第1部分有五种
默认情况下，第一个是正确的
about these are all explained in v-folds
tutorial part 1 so there are five kinds
角v形折叠这部分解释
1秒是可爱的角度默认值
tutorial part 1 so there are five kinds
of default the first is the the right
在第1部分中也对此进行了解释
第三是尖V形折叠
of default the first is the the right
angle v-folds this is explained in part
将在本教程中处理
第四个是钝角v折
angle v-folds this is explained in part
1 the second is the cute angle default
我们也要处理这个
教程，最后是不对称的
1 the second is the cute angle default
this is also explained in part 1 the
v-fold这将在v-folds教程中
第三部分好吧，我们将开始
this is also explained in part 1 the
third is the pointed v-fold this we're
进行尖锐的V形折叠，所以从
底页将卡片对折
third is the pointed v-fold this we're
going to deal with in this tutorial the
需要测量无需得分
卡片折痕重160 g时的重量
going to deal with in this tutorial the
fourth is the obtuse angle v-fold this
它真的可以将其完全折叠
本身再折一次就不能折痕
fourth is the obtuse angle v-fold this
also we're going to deal with in this
它太多了，所以将其自身折叠起来
多几次，真正折皱
also we're going to deal with in this
tutorial and finally it's the asymmetric
好吧，这是基础表
褶皱得好意味着
tutorial and finally it's the asymmetric
v-fold this will be in v-folds tutorial
弹出窗口会移动得更甜美，所以我们
最好还是说一个红色的
v-fold this will be in v-folds tutorial
part 3 okay we're going to start by
您的卡片再次无需
措施只是切成两半
part 3 okay we're going to start by
making a pointed v-fold so start with
将其对折，无需测量
与所有折痕一样，再次通过肉眼观察
making a pointed v-fold so start with
the base sheet fold the card in half no
折起来真的很彻底
它回到自己
the base sheet fold the card in half no
need to measure no need to score with
这次你从角落折叠
拐弯，所以你在做一个对角线
need to measure no need to score with
this weight of cards at 160 g SN crease
用它折角
折成两半所以没有错误的方法
this weight of cards at 160 g SN crease
it really thoroughly fold it back on
这样做是因为它是对称的
可以以任何一种方式将其折叠起来
it really thoroughly fold it back on
itself crease it again you can't crease
同样，当您打开它时，
箭头所有三个折痕都是
itself crease it again you can't crease
it too much so fold it back up itself a
在同一地点开会
再增加对角线的折痕
it too much so fold it back up itself a
couple more times and really crease it
你可以再加强一次
现在，这将坐在您的身上
couple more times and really crease it
well this is this is the base sheet
这样的页面，所以一个问题是
紧你想要它的实际形状是什么
well this is this is the base sheet
having it well creased means that the
您想要的弹出窗口，您想要一个真正的
紧密的V形折叠还是真的
having it well creased means that the
pop-up will move more sweetly so we
扁平的形状甚至可以一直走
平，它仍然可以工作，所以我去
pop-up will move more sweetly so we
might as well make a say a red one take
对于这样的事情第二
问题是你在做什么
might as well make a say a red one take
your sheet of cards again no need to
襟翼可以剪下来
变成下面的v的窄窄瓣
your sheet of cards again no need to
measure just cut it in half
它，或者您可以将它们放宽
您可以使用这些折叠来制作
fold it in half no need to measure just
柜台折起来，所以我要去做
把它变成反折，所以我们
fold it in half no need to measure just
do it by eye again as with all creases
开始只是把猫切成
折边所以说我们只是做几个
do it by eye again as with all creases
crease it really really thoroughly fold
像这样在这里折起来只是折痕
很好，我已经完成了两次切割
crease it really really thoroughly fold
it back on itself
在不同的长度，以便给
我们的形状略有不同
this time you make the fold from corner
弹出窗口将其打开并通过
所以这是另一个
this time you make the fold from corner
to corner so you're doing a diagonal
这就是我们的形状
要在最上面折痕上加油
to corner so you're doing a diagonal
fold corner to corner with it with it
现在可以在底部折痕上做同样的事情
底部的两个折痕，所以如果我们想要的话
fold corner to corner with it with it
folded in half so there's no wrong way
都是对称的，我们两者兼而有之
折叠成两个外皮瓣将其折叠起来
folded in half so there's no wrong way
to do this because it's symmetrical it
一些削减只是做几个
这里有很大的空间
to do this because it's symmetrical it
can go either way fold it back on itself
创造力和理解力
真的是一个非常简单的选择
can go either way fold it back on itself
again so when you open it up you have an
但是你知道如果你自己做
真的可以和你一起玩
again so when you open it up you have an
arrow all three all three creases are
可以使它们更长或更窄
有各种各样的选择，所以我们将
arrow all three all three creases are
meeting at the same point and those
打开此一推
二三四把这些推下来
meeting at the same point and those
extra creases the diagonal ones again
这是你现在要拥有的形状
同样，您可以决定要这些
extra creases the diagonal ones again
you can reinforce those one more time
设计中还剩下其他襟翼
否则您可能会决定修剪它们，以便
now this is going to sit on your on your
我要再修剪一次
我会遵循这种非常
now this is going to sit on your on your
page like this so one question is how
尖尖的形状，所以我只是要
像这样切成这样
page like this so one question is how
tight you want it what actual shape of
这就是您的弹出窗口
像现在一样，您可以决定要
tight you want it what actual shape of
pop-up you want do you want a really
它真的很紧还是你想要一个
相当宽的形状，所以我要去
pop-up you want do you want a really
tight V fold or do you want a really
像这样的东西
首先将所有这些粘贴到一侧
tight V fold or do you want a really
flat shape you can even go all the way
您需要的所有弹出窗口都需要对称
所以我们只是将一侧涂上
flat shape you can even go all the way
flat and it will still work so I'll go
粘到我倾向于的折痕
用我的小手指，然后我所有的
flat and it will still work so I'll go
for something like this the second
其他手指没有胶水，我
我可以用它们来触摸其他东西吗
for something like this the second
question is what you do with the with
没有汽车粘在他们身上
我们去
question is what you do with the with
the flaps you can either cut them down
一侧向下粘贴，也许将其移到
多一点确保中央
the flaps you can either cut them down
into narrow narrow flaps of v underneath
折痕与中央对齐
基地之谷
into narrow narrow flaps of v underneath
it or you can leave them out wide and
将整个东西折叠起来
位置
it or you can leave them out wide and
you can use these these folds for making
将胶水放在另一个标签上
将胶水涂抹到折痕上
you can use these these folds for making
that counter folds in so I'm going to do
将其折叠到关闭位置并
关闭基地，现在就在这里
that counter folds in so I'm going to do
that turn it into counter folds so we
也许你可以离开这些柜台
像它们一样折叠，它们只是一部分
that turn it into counter folds so we
start just cut into the cat into the
设计的替代方案，您可以使用
他们作为肌肉来提升其他部分
start just cut into the cat into the
folded edge so say we just do a couple
卡，所以我们将尝试玩
加上一点，所以拿一块
folded edge so say we just do a couple
like this here fold it over just crease
卡只是剪了一些玩
这些实际上可以是任何
like this here fold it over just crease
it well this one I've made the two cuts
调整任何形状的大小完全取决于您
我只是在做一些随机的事情
it well this one I've made the two cuts
at different lengths so that will give
在这里，所以我们把胶水放在
最小的表面，不要放在上面
at different lengths so that will give
us a slightly different shape in the
大表面贴在你身上
把胶水放到小小的
us a slightly different shape in the
pop-up open it up and push those through
柜台折叠的表面，您可以
只是把棍子多放一点
pop-up open it up and push those through
so that's one this is the other
到那也可以做同样的事情
另一面是你的卡片
so that's one this is the other
so that's the that's the shape we're
可以看到它有点薄
一块的长度，所以我可能会修剪
so that's the that's the shape we're
going to get on it on the top crease you
一分钟下来，他们把一个
在那里，您实际上可以使用其他
going to get on it on the top crease you
can now do the same on the bottom crease
柜台的其他面折叠成
好吧，让我们把这对夫妇
can now do the same on the bottom crease
the bottom two creases so if we want it
只是为了您可以看到所有
可能的选择，所以把胶水涂在那些
the bottom two creases so if we want it
all symmetric we do it all with the two
两个让你举起一块
这样，另一个在这里
all symmetric we do it all with the two
folds to two outer flaps fold it up make
这样举起来，你也可以
玩这些飞机
folds to two outer flaps fold it up make
some cuts into those just do a couple
我们已经创建
在前四名中，我只做一个
some cuts into those just do a couple
here there's a lot of room for
更窄的一块适合
折成两半
here there's a lot of room for
creativity in this and understanding
实际上并不需要一半
您可以在任何地方使用电话
creativity in this and understanding
something really a really simple option
你想要一个更不对称的设计
沿某处折叠
something really a really simple option
but you know if you make your own you
这条胶水放进去，你可以
只是把它塞在里面然后粘在里面
but you know if you make your own you
can really play around with these you
在添加完这些片段后，请关闭
底座并用力按，使所有
can really play around with these you
can make them longer narrower multiple
对于胶合是这样等等
我们是
can make them longer narrower multiple
there's all sorts of options so we'll
这只是一个抽象的形状，所以你
可以在任何地方看到它
there's all sorts of options so we'll
open this one up push these through one
没有正确的方法，没有错误的方法，所以你
可能会选择像你这样看
open this one up push these through one
two three four push these ones down so
可能会选择这样看
同样，也许这甚至是它
two three four push these ones down so
this is a shape you're gonna have now
只是抽象的耶抽象的形状所以你
可以平等地做自己喜欢的事
this is a shape you're gonna have now
again you can decide that you want these
这两个平面可以扩展，所以
你只需要几个
again you can decide that you want these
other flaps left as part of the design
小块，我将胶水涂在上面
进入视频
other flaps left as part of the design
or you might decide to trim them down so
这样你就可以像
那，也许另一个类似的
or you might decide to trim them down so
I'm going to trim them down so again
另一边虽然不平坦
我把它修剪下来，所以有一点
I'm going to trim them down so again
I'll just follow this sort of very
V形折叠，现在我将向您展示
这个传播是几个例子
I'll just follow this sort of very
pointy pointy shape so I'm just going to
这一切都是尖锐的v错
结束时，您已经
pointy pointy shape so I'm just going to
cut it like this to the to the point so
每边的反折是
用来举起手臂和腿，这是
cut it like this to the to the point so
this is what your pop-up is going to be
换个角度来看，
非常尖端被切断，这使头部
this is what your pop-up is going to be
like now again you can decide you want
所以这是几个尖锐的V形折叠
书上有这十个
like now again you can decide you want
it really tight or do you want quite a
小怪物，在这一个
在这种情况下V点会折叠
it really tight or do you want quite a
quite a wide shape so I'm gonna go for
这是拍过的皮瓣
过去一直坚持下去，他们是
quite a wide shape so I'm gonna go for
something like this
设计，而不是做
柜台下跌件已被卡在
something like this
start by gluing one side with all these
向前伸出的每一侧
头只是在说，你可以看看
start by gluing one side with all these
all pop ups you need you need symmetry
它结束，看看它是如何工作的
你就直接用了
all pop ups you need you need symmetry
so we're just glue one side smear the
作为背景的书，这是丛林
天海伦轰炸机和行李箱
so we're just glue one side smear the
glue right up to the crease I tend to
树被指定为V折，
就像其他v形折边添加到
glue right up to the crease I tend to
use my little finger so then all my
提高数字，削减插槽
使其四肢伸出来
use my little finger so then all my
other fingers stay free from glue and I
无论如何，重点是
树的树干被指定为V折
other fingers stay free from glue and I
can I can use them to touch other things
最后是《穿靴子的猫》，作者是
Wojtek cabassa捷克斯洛伐克工作
can I can use them to touch other things
without cars sticking to them so there
在60年代，这是两点
查看文件，这显然是
without cars sticking to them so there
we go
指定的错误
这是一个观点折叠
we go
stick one side down maybe move it in a
大量切掉v文件有
趋于一致的折痕
stick one side down maybe move it in a
little bit more make sure the central
脊椎上的相同点，如果
跟随这里的折痕和这个
little bit more make sure the central
crease is lined up with the Central
这个你会发现他们都见面
相同
crease is lined up with the Central
Valley of the base
从这个债券，所以这是一个重点
现在折，我们继续往下看
Valley of the base
fold the whole thing into its closed
角度默认为这个，但这是
钝角V折每个角度
fold the whole thing into its closed
position
中央折痕的一侧弹出
超过90度
position
put glue under put glue on the other tab
不寻常的机制，您看不到
我经常会告诉你如何做一个
smear the glue to the to the creases
这些，所以要打好基础
我们拿出一半的时间
fold it into its closed position and
张纸在中间折叠
完全弄皱，然后
fold it into its closed position and
close the base so here it is now you
这次是折叠的边缘
从大约三分之一开始
close the base so here it is now you
might you might leave these counter
向下折叠到
卡，所以在这里它折叠好时
might you might leave these counter
folds just as they are they're just part
当您打开它时，您会看到
你有一个向上的箭头
folds just as they are they're just part
of the design alternatively you can use
大多与他们成锐角
v形折叠，您将向下指
of the design alternatively you can use
them as muscle to lift other pieces of
正常的箭头就是
您通常在寻找，但在此
them as muscle to lift other pieces of
cards so we'll just try playing around
折痕形成箭头
从现在开始切出
cards so we'll just try playing around
with that for a bit so take a piece of
所有的折痕都满足了您
薄的楔子，您可以将粘合片切到
with that for a bit so take a piece of
card just cut some pieces to play with
底部切断末端哦，我会做的
有点紧，所以这是你的
card just cut some pieces to play with
and these can these can actually be any
是你的钝角，我们让这个
重新增加这些沙落点
and these can these can actually be any
size any shape it's completely up to you
如果您的
折叠足够折痕离开
size any shape it's completely up to you
I'm just doing something fairly random
弹出窗口无法打开
衣服很好所以很重要
I'm just doing something fairly random
here so we put the put the glue on the
要增加它，这将坐下
在这样的页面上，您可以
here so we put the put the glue on the
smallest surface you don't put it on the
宽，你可以收紧，但如果你
太宽，你会看到它开始升起
smallest surface you don't put it on the
big surface which is sticking on you you
离开页面，因此根据角度
你做了，这将决定如何
big surface which is sticking on you you
put the glue onto the small small
广，你可以走了，我们再次坚持下去
一方面，这种对称总是
put the glue onto the small small
surface of the counter fold and you can
重要的是通过削减
折成两半，我们得到
surface of the counter fold and you can
just stick the stick the extra piece
弹出窗口和现在的对称角度
我们坚持下去的方式
just stick the stick the extra piece
onto that might as well do the same on
在裤子上获得对称角度
在那里它粘在一侧
onto that might as well do the same on
the other side the card is slightly you
确保中央折痕
弹出窗口与沟壑对齐
the other side the card is slightly you
can see it's slightly thin for this this
基础折叠的整体关闭
很好地按一下，将胶水粘在另一个上
can see it's slightly thin for this this
length of piece so I might just trim
其他标签
将胶水涂抹到折痕处
length of piece so I might just trim
that down in a minute they put one on
那很重要
折叠很烂，我们去了两个单
that down in a minute they put one on
there and you can actually use the other
V折这很有趣
因为中央的折痕
there and you can actually use the other
the other faces of the counter fold as
弹出窗口向后倒落
中央沟将倾斜
the other faces of the counter fold as
well so let's just put the couple coming
向后是直角V折
所以这是一个版本，这些是正确的
well so let's just put the couple coming
up just so you can see all the all the
角度v折叠底部a上的角度
90度，而在这个角度上
up just so you can see all the all the
possible options so put glue on those
超过90个，而这些是因为
因为它倒退了，我
possible options so put glue on those
two so you have a piece of lifting up
想想你想弹出的更高
必须离前端越近
two so you have a piece of lifting up
like that and another one on here
是的，我只会在几个
钝角V的示例对此有误
lifting up like that and you can also
是一个，你可以看到它只是向后倾斜
稍微地一点，以便很好地工作
lifting up like that and you can also
play with these these some planes that
这个设计我有一本书
他们作为纠结V折叠和尖
play with these these some planes that
we've created
V折，所以这就是书
是Chuck Murphy的Bow Wow，这是
we've created
in the top four so I'll just make one
是在三角形下面吗？
那里的金字塔是尖的V形折叠
in the top four so I'll just make one
more really narrow piece that will fit
狗是钝角V Falls
最好的方式就是看
more really narrow piece that will fit
into that fold it in half though again
在设计的背面，在那里
可以看到中央的折痕
into that fold it in half though again
it doesn't actually need to be in half
狗向后倾斜，所以狗是
钝角V折金字塔是一个
it doesn't actually need to be in half
you can have a phone anywhere on it if
尖头v形折叠，正好适合
v形折叠我所有的信息
you can have a phone anywhere on it if
you wanted a more asymmetric design just
给你在展位我的书弹出
纸力学设计
you wanted a more asymmetric design just
make a fold somewhere somewhere along